Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Well, come on! What have you done already?
Monster!
Tell me, boy, what are you?
I am... I'm somebody who was born without a single drop of magic power.
And I'm still gonna be the Wizard King. I'll fight and bleed all I have to. But I will prove that I can do it!
Mars, when you grow up, what do you want to be?
I... I live only to destroy!
That's why you live? To destroy? While the Wizard King lives to protect his kingdom and his people!
We'll keep everyone in the country safe. That's why we were born, right?
I will never lose! Not to somebody like you!
You're in my way! Be gone! Be gone! Pebble!
Sure, I might be a pebble! But if so, I'm going to be the pebble that shatters the diamond!
The diamond!
You're poopy!
Enough!
If youлично, I'd be more than anything!
How you must escape!
Last day in hastily那 need foom.
Mes hosted by humanoid morte
xittle
foreign
xial
who
y
and
Oh
There that should hold him
You sure that binding spell is gonna be enough are you questioning the strength of my magic?
It's a sturdy spell that won't be broken by an injured mage. Plus I have his grimoire
Okay, okay defensive much here have some good. I don't want your half chewed leftovers, you know I
Think I'll pass I'm so relieved that none of us were seriously injured
Are you sure you should be up and about already? Oh, yes, it's fine. I'm mostly healed by now
I have you to thank for protecting me so valiantly
No, I didn't do anything special. I just couldn't leave a dimwit like you to fend for herself
Well, you have my gratitude
Fine, whatever Asta do you think you could do something about yourself already?
Geez, what am I doing wrong this time?
Just look at the way you're dressed. Why are you blushing when I'm the one half naked? Don't be ridiculous. I am not blushing
My robe though
God, just look at it. The poor thing got seriously torn up
Magnus totally gonna kill me for this
Vanessa'll fix it up when we get back
You think she can it's in really bad shape?
Shameful I still cannot believe we needed the assistance of the black bulls
As I was certain we would we arrived here first and thus are the winners of the competition
However, this once I will allow you to accompany us into the treasure hall
Come on four eyes. Could you be any more high and mighty?
Thank you so very much you enormous jerk
You're welcome and shut your mouth before it gets you in trouble. Oh, have I upset you so spectacles?
I'm terribly sorry. I would chastise you for that, but I simply don't have the time for petty adolescent squabbles with a black bull runt
Oh, please sir, spectacles. I beg your forgiveness. We're not just involved. We're committed
Now that is taking it too far. I'll show you too far
Enough, we're off to the treasure hall. Let's go
Whatever's hidden in there. We're gonna claim it in the name of the clover kingdom's magic night
Will you stop yelling? You're one to talk loudmouth
So how do we get in?
There's probably a cypher here somewhere that will allow us to open the door go on and find it four eyes be quiet
And it's not four eyes. It's Klaus
Looks like it's made of magic so you should be able to slice right through have that
All right, please as if you'd be able to counter such powerful magic
There see
Oh
This is awesome
It's like a mountain of treasure
Hey careful, we don't know what's in there
It's so beautiful
Look at this bubble thing. What's it even supposed to do?
Hmm
Enough! Cease your fiddling! There could be priceless magical artifacts in here
Poking around some is not gonna hurt Captain Shortfuse
Use my proper name
Okay, Mr. Spitz
Don't think I won't hurt you
Oh, I'm scared now
You wretch!
See, I was right. You got a short fuse
Only because you insist on baiting me you insufferable twerp
What's this? That writing? I've never seen it before
It's gone
What's going on, you know? What was that light?
I don't know
You shouldn't have touched that
Now put it back where it belongs
Come on, quit it, Nero! You're picking me to death here!
Okay, what about it?
His grimoire
And what a singular one it is
All patched together
Interesting
He got the four-leaf clover
And he got something that's so dirty it's barely recognizable
I guess you never can tell
Anything good?
Ugh
This magic
Quick, get back!
No! Impossible!
My binding spell should have held him
He was unconscious
Injured
How did he recover in such a short time?
Wait
Is that
Flame recovery magic?
But how?
Each mage can have only one magic attribute
The four elements
Fire
Wind
Water
Earth
A mage is imbued with mana from one of these
The attributes interact in specific ways
Fire is strong against wind but weak to water
It is a known law that a mage can only use one kind of magic stemming from one of these attributes or its derivatives
Yet in defiance of that law he can wield two types of magic
And while he clearly commands attack magic
He can cast recovery spells too?
Inconceivable
Those jewels
Is this what came of the diamond kingdom's experiments?
Mars
I know you'll be a wonderful warrior
I'm sorry Mars
But this is the only way
You have to die
If I put out those flames it should weaken him
Noelle's hit
Noelle!
Damn you!
How dare you hurt my friend!
I've figured out what your ability is now
Seems that sword of yours destroys any and all magic
But what if the magic is faster than your blade?
I know..
So quick!
HOW DARE YOU HURT MY FRIEND!
Are you ready?
Only those who are strong will survive.
The weak deserve death.
Noelle!
Only those who are strong will survive.
We're not done! Don't give up!
There's no time for Dream Healing Flower Cradle.
Plant recovery magic, Princess Healing Flower Rove.
Stay strong for me.
This is the best recovery spell I can muster now.
It has to work!
Please, you can't die!
Keep fighting!
What are you doing, Mimosa?
Really, I swear.
Are you such a dimwit you can't even walk?
Come on.
Thank you, Noelle.
I am a bit clumsy sometimes.
That's marvelous, Mimosa.
Incredible!
To be capable of such powerful recovery magic at her age.
Given her strength as a royal, she may very well grow skilled enough to be able to heal any wound.
Now that would be something to see.
Have you heard, though?
It appears the second daughter of the Silva House, a girl around Mimosa's age,
lacks sufficient control over her magic power.
Apparently, she has to practice daily.
For somebody like that to be born into the royal family.
I suppose we of House Vermillion are the true royalty of the Clover Kingdom.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
If it were me, I probably would have given up.
Members of our class look down on those who put forth effort.
Hard work is for the weak and powerless, not for royalty.
To us, everything should come easily.
But you...
You've always worked hard!
And I have always admired you for it!
Only those who are strong will survive.
The weak deserve death.
If I could only use my Grimoire!
My sword...
Noelle...
Mimosa...
He was right about that magic being fast.
My sword's too big and heavy to keep up with it.
He changed his fighting style to counter mine.
I need to do the same thing.
But how?
Nero?
The Internationer's
You have to die.
Only those who are strong will survive.
The weak deserve death!
Mimosa!
Where did that sword come from?
Leave them alone!
Your new opponent...
is right here!
What for me?
Be gone, boy!
I can bust through his attack spells,
but he's still got that recovery magic.
I can't finish him off!
What now?
Why are you just sitting there, insect?
Don't strain yourself!
You're awake!
Listen to me.
I am royalty, Asta.
Asta, and you are the first commoner I've accepted.
Now get moving.
And don't you dare give up until you beat him.
Understand?
Yeah, I'll bring this guy down.
And I'll get one or two hits in for you while I'm at it.
Give up.
You can't win.
I live to destroy the weak.
Well, you're not gonna destroy me!
I may not have any magic power,
but what I do have...
are my friends!
Do you think that's enough to defeat me?
Wait, how is that possible?
I didn't think he had any magic.
A water-based slashing attack?
Did he borrow Noelle's magic?
What in the world is that sword?
I don't really know how, but I did it.
I'm dead.
What's happening?
But yeah, she's...
My Girl!
Eso es solo
I can find a place to go
消えそうな光でも闇を照らす力が
繋がって時の流れを変える
I'm living in you
色褪せない場所に
Brain for yourself
終わらない夢を掴むため
進むべき道があるなら
Do you wanna drive? Do you wanna drive?
このままどこを待ってても
僕の命が終わるまで
どんな痛みも受け入れよう
We can try again
たとえ明日が見えなくても
声にならない想いを抱いて
叫び続ける in my heart
Clover Cliff
Long Suffering
One of my more useful spells
Flame Recovery Magic Phoenix Robe
I have to say, that looks quite warm.
It is.
And also rather heavy.
Very heavy.
What's more, if my face itches, I can't scratch it.
Only those who are strong will survive.
The weak deserve to die.
Pebbles that will be grounded to gravel and scattered by the wind.
Black Clover, page 19.
Destruction and salvation.
My magic will destroy all.